https://www.osullivandavies.com.au/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Get in touch with us and we'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Name*Email Address*
Phone Number*MessagePrivacyBy submitting this form, you are consenting to our Privacy Policy.NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Make An Enquiry
Key ServicesForward Planning
Spousal Maintenance
Property Settlement
Pre-Nuptial and Financial Agreements
Occupation of Property
Mediation and Arbitration
Injunctions and Restraining Orders
Name*Email Address*
Phone Number*MessagePrivacyBy submitting this form, you are consenting to our Privacy Policy.NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
+61 89426 4711
About Us
Services
Mediation and Arbitration
Mediation and Arbitration
Property Settlement
Property Settlement
Forward Planning
Contact
About UsServicesMediation and ArbitrationMediation and ArbitrationProperty SettlementProperty SettlementForward PlanningDivorceDe facto RelationshipsPre-Nuptial and Financial AgreementsInjunctions and Restraining OrdersSpousal MaintenancePreservation of AssetsChildrenArrangements for ChildrenChild SupportEnforcements of Agreements and OrdersOccupation of PropertyRelocation of ChildrenOur TeamPublicationsContact
Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of individuals. Generally, we do not release personal information. However in response to a legal requirement, in the case of an emergency or in exceptional circumstances a partner may at their discretion authorise the release of personal information.
We may make a record of your visit to this site and log your visit for statistical and business purposes. Such information includes your server address, domain name, IP address, the date and time of your visit, pages accessed, documents downloaded, previous site visited and the type of browser used.
If you send us an email message we will record your email address. We will only use your email address for the purpose for which it was provided. We will not use it for any other purpose without your express approval.
Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to our site. If you do not wish information to be gathered on a cookie it is possible to disable the acceptance of cookies by your web browser. If you want to do this you should contact your ISP. If this site uses a cookie to deliver contents we consider will interest you, the cookie may also be used for authentication.
Personal information that you supply through this site will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and to assist us to conduct our business. This may include analysing information obtained on the site to determine the effectiveness of the site and to modify the site to improve the service that it provides.
We will not disclose your personal information to a third party except in accordance with this notice.
